<articles>
  <topic id="2">
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18348679</pmid>
      <title>Potential therapeutic targets for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10401786</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa induces a cytoplasmic localization of D1 dopamine receptors in striatal neurons in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16857573</pmid>
      <title>Continuous dopamine-receptor treatment of Parkinson's disease: scientific rationale and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15265382</pmid>
      <title>Single photon emission computer tomography of dopamine transporters in monkeys and humans with 99mTc-TRODAT-1.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7726209</pmid>
      <title>No allelic association between Parkinson's disease and dopamine D2, D3, and D4 receptor gene polymorphisms.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18325544</pmid>
      <title>Spreading activation of lexical-semantic networks in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19995871</pmid>
      <title>Enhanced frontal function in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17707679</pmid>
      <title>The rationale for continuous dopaminergic stimulation in advanced Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10086151</pmid>
      <title>[Drug therapy in Parkinson's disease].
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9592785</pmid>
      <title>Null hypothesis of husband-wife concordance of Parkinson's disease in 1,000 married couples over age 50 in Spain.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3290993</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19356748</pmid>
      <title>Semantic activation in Parkinson's disease patients on and off levodopa.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11261503</pmid>
      <title>Biochemical variations in the synaptic level of dopamine precede motor fluctuations in Parkinson's disease: PET evidence of increased dopamine turnover.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20013480</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic modulation of the planning phase of skill acquisition in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12207999</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and the representation of the upper visual field: evidence from vertical bisection errors in unilateral Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16798054</pmid>
      <title>Estimating the value of novel interventions for Parkinson's disease: an early decision-making model with application to dopamine cell replacement.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20155994</pmid>
      <title>Gene therapy in Parkinson's disease: rationale and current status.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16458973</pmid>
      <title>What has been learnt from study of dopamine receptors in Parkinson's disease?
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>22014434</pmid>
      <title>Advances in imaging in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8489408</pmid>
      <title>Imaging of D2 dopamine receptors of patients with Parkinson's disease using single photon emission computed tomography and iodobenzamide I 123.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6492486</pmid>
      <title>Study on the striatal dopamine availability in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18781671</pmid>
      <title>The history of dopamine and levodopa in the treatment of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1378662</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor interactions: some implications for the treatment of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20965203</pmid>
      <title>Altruistic punishment in patients with Parkinson's disease with and without impulsive behaviour.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12083948</pmid>
      <title>Gene therapy for Parkinson's disease: current status and future potential.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6933216</pmid>
      <title>Parkinson's disease: unanswered questions.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21259269</pmid>
      <title>Cell transplantation and gene therapy in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10762131</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-mediated gene regulation in models of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19131046</pmid>
      <title>The hypothesis of the genesis of motor complications and continuous dopaminergic stimulation in the treatment of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9591518</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa therapy: consequences of the nonphysiologic replacement of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20471298</pmid>
      <title>Trials of neuroprotective therapies for Parkinson's disease: problems and limitations.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1358615</pmid>
      <title>Early therapy for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930746</pmid>
      <title>CNS compensation to dopamine neuron loss in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20368163</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine gene therapy for Parkinson's disease in a nonhuman primate without associated dyskinesia.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1320533</pmid>
      <title>Mechanisms of neuronal loss in Parkinson's disease: a neuroanatomical-biochemical perspective.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12464115</pmid>
      <title>5-hydroxytryptamine (5-HT, serotonin) and Parkinson's disease - opportunities for novel therapeutics to reduce the problems of levodopa therapy.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15247533</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine dysregulation syndrome in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18322366</pmid>
      <title>Basic research on dopamine in Parkinson's disease and the discovery of the nigrostriatal dopamine pathway: the view of an eyewitness.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8714754</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors--the present state of research and perspectives.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12846971</pmid>
      <title>PET studies on the function of dopamine in health and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11498597</pmid>
      <title>Expectation and dopamine release: mechanism of the placebo effect in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11532645</pmid>
      <title>Parkinson's disease: medical and surgical treatment.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8450991</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-related personality traits in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3378138</pmid>
      <title>'Frontal' cognitive function in patients with Parkinson's disease 'on' and 'off' levodopa.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6127822</pmid>
      <title>[Problems and future perspectives in the treatment of Parkinson's disease].
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7044903</pmid>
      <title>Parkinson's disease as a model for changes in dopamine receptor dynamics with aging.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9067850</pmid>
      <title>Pathophysiology and management of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="12">
    <article>
      <pmid>20926973</pmid>
      <title>Intense dopamine innervation of the subventricular zone in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10838590</pmid>
      <title>Neuronal cell death in Huntington's disease: a potential role for dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9822765</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine modulates the susceptibility of striatal neurons to 3-nitropropionic acid in the rat model of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10829080</pmid>
      <title>Severe deficiencies in dopamine signaling in presymptomatic Huntington's disease mice.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17065224</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine enhances motor and neuropathological consequences of polyglutamine expanded huntingtin.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2445259</pmid>
      <title>Elevated serotonin and reduced dopamine in subregionally divided Huntington's disease striatum.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17652581</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic signaling and striatal neurodegeneration in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20886576</pmid>
      <title>Extrastriatal dopamine D(2) receptor binding in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9152043</pmid>
      <title>Localization of dopamine receptors and associated mRNA in transplants of human fetal striatal tissue in rodents with experimental Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17707679</pmid>
      <title>The rationale for continuous dopaminergic stimulation in advanced Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1363335</pmid>
      <title>Neuroleptic treatment is an unlikely cause of elevated dopamine in thalamus of schizophrenic subjects.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21256185</pmid>
      <title>Impaired dopamine release and uptake in R6/1 Huntington's disease model mice.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19410615</pmid>
      <title>Striatal dopamine level contributes to hydroxyl radical generation and subsequent neurodegeneration in the striatum in 3-nitropropionic acid-induced Huntington's disease in rats.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16573654</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine release is severely compromised in the R6/2 mouse model of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9591518</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa therapy: consequences of the nonphysiologic replacement of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>14597227</pmid>
      <title>Analysis of cellular, transgenic and human models of Huntington's disease reveals tyrosine hydroxylase alterations and substantia nigra neuropathology.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11719268</pmid>
      <title>Brain-derived neurotrophic factor inhibits apoptosis and dopamine-induced free radical production in striatal neurons but does not prevent cell death.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12460553</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for dysfunction of the nigrostriatal pathway in the R6/1 line of transgenic Huntington's disease mice.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2939198</pmid>
      <title>Striatal dopamine and homovanillic acid in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9266732</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine D1 and D2 receptor gene expression in the striatum in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10401786</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa induces a cytoplasmic localization of D1 dopamine receptors in striatal neurons in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8172940</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine D1 receptor number--a sensitive PET marker for early brain degeneration in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15350965</pmid>
      <title>Synergistic effects of dopamine and Zn2+ on the induction of PC12 cell death and dopamine depletion in the striatum: possible implication in the pathogenesis of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3614661</pmid>
      <title>Fluctuations in plasma dopamine level impair memory in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17046697</pmid>
      <title>Rapid alterations in corticostriatal ensemble coordination during acute dopamine-dependent motor dysfunction.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15681811</pmid>
      <title>The degeneration of dopamine neurons in Parkinson's disease: insights from embryology and evolution of the mesostriatocortical system.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11406606</pmid>
      <title>Expanded CAG repeats in exon 1 of the Huntington's disease gene stimulate dopamine-mediated striatal neuron autophagy and degeneration.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9126061</pmid>
      <title>PET study of the pre- and post-synaptic dopaminergic markers for the neurodegenerative process in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18781680</pmid>
      <title>Striatal and extrastriatal dopamine in the basal ganglia: an overview of its anatomical organization in normal and Parkinsonian brains.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6152262</pmid>
      <title>Neuropeptides in dopamine-containing regions of the brain.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8010587</pmid>
      <title>Cellular and molecular mechanisms of impaired dopaminergic function during aging.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15130772</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine toxicity involves mitochondrial complex I inhibition: implications to dopamine-related neuropsychiatric disorders.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1838580</pmid>
      <title>Heterogeneous dopamine receptor changes in early and late Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2530315</pmid>
      <title>Lack of GTP-insensitive D2 dopamine receptors in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9349549</pmid>
      <title>In vivo electrochemical measurement of the long-lasting release of dopamine and serotonin induced by intrastriatal kainic acid.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19362126</pmid>
      <title>In vivo dopamine release and uptake impairments in rats treated with 3-nitropropionic acid.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1823144</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for plasticity of the dopaminergic system in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11052221</pmid>
      <title>Electrophysiology of dopamine in normal and denervated striatal neurons.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2908162</pmid>
      <title>Synaptic and non-synaptic striatal dopamine D2 receptors: possible implications in normal and pathological behaviour.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8531220</pmid>
      <title>GM1 ganglioside rescues substantia nigra pars compacta neurons and increases dopamine synthesis in residual nigrostriatal dopaminergic neurons in MPTP-treated mice.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20368163</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine gene therapy for Parkinson's disease in a nonhuman primate without associated dyskinesia.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10701753</pmid>
      <title>Phenotypical characterization of the neurons expressing the D1 and D2 dopamine receptors in the monkey striatum.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10762131</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-mediated gene regulation in models of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2919185</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine turnover and glutathione oxidation: implications for Parkinson disease.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9771125</pmid>
      <title>[Functional role and pharmacological regulation of the dopaminergic system of the brain].
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="20">
    <article>
      <pmid>6147948</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-beta-hydroxylase and acetylcholinesterase activities of cerebrospinal fluid in Alzheimer's disease.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7712161</pmid>
      <title>Cerebrospinal dopamine metabolites in rats after intrastriatal administration of 6-hydroxydopamine or 1-methyl-4-phenylpyridinium ion.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3982644</pmid>
      <title>CSF dopamine-beta-hydroxylase activity in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1922797</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine sulfate in ventricular cerebrospinal fluid and motor function in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3678940</pmid>
      <title>Biogenic amines in cerebrospinal fluid and plasma of patients with dementia of Alzheimer type.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>160445</pmid>
      <title>Interactions between central monoaminergic systems: dopamine-serotonin.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18207455</pmid>
      <title>Circadian rhythm of CSF monoamines and hypocretin-1 in restless legs syndrome and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2314121</pmid>
      <title>Adrenal medullary transplantation into the brain for treatment of Parkinson's disease: clinical outcome and neurochemical studies.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>907536</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine turnover and the relief of parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15159499</pmid>
      <title>Infantile Parkinsonism-dystonia and elevated dopamine metabolites in CSF.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2579626</pmid>
      <title>CSF monamine metabolites in movement disorders and normal aging.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1153623</pmid>
      <title>Assessment of cerebrospinal fluid levels of dopamine metabolites by gas chromatography.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7908885</pmid>
      <title>Cerebrospinal fluid from patients with Parkinson's disease alters the survival of dopamine neurons in mesencephalic culture.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2089111</pmid>
      <title>Effect of adrenal-caudate transplantation on CSF levels of salsolinol sulfate in patients with Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10442254</pmid>
      <title>Opposite changes in dopamine metabolites and met-enkephalin levels in the ventricular CSF of patients subjected to thalamic electrical stimulation.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6157799</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine (DA) and serotonin metabolic levels in the cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) in Alzheimer's presenile dementia under basic conditions and after stimulation with cerebral cortex phospholipids (BC-PL).
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15200114</pmid>
      <title>The mechanism and effect of chronic electrical stimulation of the globus pallidus for treatment of Parkinson disease.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6420835</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine/L-dopa ratio in cerebrospinal fluid of parkinsonian patients treated with L-dopa + benserazide.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2290957</pmid>
      <title>Improvements in MPTP-induced object retrieval deficits and behavioral deficits after fetal nigral grafting in monkeys.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>143508</pmid>
      <title>Biochemical aspects of Huntington's chorea.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15130772</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine toxicity involves mitochondrial complex I inhibition: implications to dopamine-related neuropsychiatric disorders.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1436520</pmid>
      <title>Markers of dopamine metabolism in Parkinson's disease. The Parkinson Study Group.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2024737</pmid>
      <title>Interrelationship between activation of dopaminergic pathways and cerebrospinal fluid concentration of dopamine tetrahydroisoquinoline metabolite salsolinol in humans: preliminary findings.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15088079</pmid>
      <title>Human genetics of plasma dopamine beta-hydroxylase activity: applications to research in psychiatry and neurology.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1247283</pmid>
      <title>Biochemical aids in the diagnosis of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2754305</pmid>
      <title>Catecholamines in CSF, plasma, and tissue after autologous transplantation of adrenal medulla to the brain in patients with Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7605589</pmid>
      <title>Markers of dopamine depletion and compensatory response in striatum and cerebrospinal fluid.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6152262</pmid>
      <title>Neuropeptides in dopamine-containing regions of the brain.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8434878</pmid>
      <title>Plasma and cerebrospinal fluid neurochemical pattern in Menkes disease.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7264660</pmid>
      <title>Highly sensitive assay for dopamine-beta-hydroxylase activity in human cerebrospinal fluid by high performance liquid chromatography-electrochemical detection: properties of the enzyme.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12200189</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-derived endogenous N-methyl-(R)-salsolinol: its role in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15790526</pmid>
      <title>Synuclein, dopamine and oxidative stress: co-conspirators in Parkinson's disease?
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2461537</pmid>
      <title>Selective attention in Alzheimer's disease: CSF correlates of behavioral impairments.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12460681</pmid>
      <title>Mitochondrial damage by nitric oxide is potentiated by dopamine in PC12 cells.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2041594</pmid>
      <title>The potential use of a dopamine neuron antibody and a striatal-derived neurotrophic factor as diagnostic markers in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8531220</pmid>
      <title>GM1 ganglioside rescues substantia nigra pars compacta neurons and increases dopamine synthesis in residual nigrostriatal dopaminergic neurons in MPTP-treated mice.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6175872</pmid>
      <title>Effects of oral L-tyrosine administration on CSF tyrosine and homovanillic acid levels in patients with Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19010710</pmid>
      <title>Correlation between changes in CSF dopamine turnover and development of dyskinesia in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6172024</pmid>
      <title>Serotonin and dopamine disturbances in patients with unipolar depression and Parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1823144</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for plasticity of the dopaminergic system in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6726279</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-beta-hydroxylase activities in serum and cerebrospinal fluid of aged and demented patients.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15681811</pmid>
      <title>The degeneration of dopamine neurons in Parkinson's disease: insights from embryology and evolution of the mesostriatocortical system.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8800434</pmid>
      <title>Laboratory examinations correlated with severity of dementia.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9620058</pmid>
      <title>Polymorphisms of dopamine receptor and transporter genes and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="23">
    <article>
      <pmid>12932859</pmid>
      <title>Neurochemical and behavioural modifications induced by scrapie infection in golden hamsters.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8099801</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and depression.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18781680</pmid>
      <title>Striatal and extrastriatal dopamine in the basal ganglia: an overview of its anatomical organization in normal and Parkinsonian brains.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1823144</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for plasticity of the dopaminergic system in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19272288</pmid>
      <title>[The relevance of dopamine agonists in the treatment of depression].
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9620058</pmid>
      <title>Polymorphisms of dopamine receptor and transporter genes and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6152262</pmid>
      <title>Neuropeptides in dopamine-containing regions of the brain.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15189334</pmid>
      <title>Could a loss of alpha-synuclein function put dopaminergic neurons at risk?
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9822765</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine modulates the susceptibility of striatal neurons to 3-nitropropionic acid in the rat model of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17707679</pmid>
      <title>The rationale for continuous dopaminergic stimulation in advanced Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12145295</pmid>
      <title>Effect of mutant alpha-synuclein on dopamine homeostasis in a new human mesencephalic cell line.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18852892</pmid>
      <title>Inhibition of alpha-synuclein fibrillization by dopamine is mediated by interactions with five C-terminal residues and with E83 in the NAC region.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17046697</pmid>
      <title>Rapid alterations in corticostriatal ensemble coordination during acute dopamine-dependent motor dysfunction.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18039462</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine differentially induces aggregation of A53T mutant and wild type alpha-synuclein: insights into the protein chemistry of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21182589</pmid>
      <title>P25alpha / TPPP expression increases plasma membrane presentation of the dopamine transporter and enhances cellular sensitivity to dopamine toxicity.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18973248</pmid>
      <title>Serotonin and dopamine transporter genes do not influence depression in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8531220</pmid>
      <title>GM1 ganglioside rescues substantia nigra pars compacta neurons and increases dopamine synthesis in residual nigrostriatal dopaminergic neurons in MPTP-treated mice.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6140979</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and depression: a review of recent evidence. I. Empirical studies.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2908162</pmid>
      <title>Synaptic and non-synaptic striatal dopamine D2 receptors: possible implications in normal and pathological behaviour.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10401786</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa induces a cytoplasmic localization of D1 dopamine receptors in striatal neurons in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15681811</pmid>
      <title>The degeneration of dopamine neurons in Parkinson's disease: insights from embryology and evolution of the mesostriatocortical system.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17290452</pmid>
      <title>Higher nigrostriatal dopamine neuron loss in early than late onset Parkinson's disease?--a [99mTc]-TRODAT-1 SPECT study.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3707090</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine denervation does not alter in vivo 3H-spiperone binding in rat striatum: implications for external imaging of dopamine receptors in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16260646</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors set the pattern of activity generated in subthalamic neurons.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12846971</pmid>
      <title>PET studies on the function of dopamine in health and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17065224</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine enhances motor and neuropathological consequences of polyglutamine expanded huntingtin.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9380062</pmid>
      <title>Association of a polymorphism in the dopamine-transporter gene with Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6254020</pmid>
      <title>Tyrosine administration increases striatal dopamine release in rats with partial nigrostriatal lesions.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15350965</pmid>
      <title>Synergistic effects of dopamine and Zn2+ on the induction of PC12 cell death and dopamine depletion in the striatum: possible implication in the pathogenesis of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21259269</pmid>
      <title>Cell transplantation and gene therapy in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15135042</pmid>
      <title>alpha-Synuclein regulation of the dopaminergic transporter: a possible role in the pathogenesis of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9591518</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa therapy: consequences of the nonphysiologic replacement of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10701753</pmid>
      <title>Phenotypical characterization of the neurons expressing the D1 and D2 dopamine receptors in the monkey striatum.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10570493</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine release from nigral transplants visualized in vivo in a Parkinson's patient.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11078922</pmid>
      <title>Cellular dopamine is increased following exposure to a factor derived from immortalized striatal neurons [corrected].
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2969952</pmid>
      <title>Mapping dopamine receptors in the human brain.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="24">
    <article>
      <pmid>17035544</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic control of sleep-wake states.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8099801</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and depression.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18781680</pmid>
      <title>Striatal and extrastriatal dopamine in the basal ganglia: an overview of its anatomical organization in normal and Parkinsonian brains.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17046697</pmid>
      <title>Rapid alterations in corticostriatal ensemble coordination during acute dopamine-dependent motor dysfunction.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1823144</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for plasticity of the dopaminergic system in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6152262</pmid>
      <title>Neuropeptides in dopamine-containing regions of the brain.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9620058</pmid>
      <title>Polymorphisms of dopamine receptor and transporter genes and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6179747</pmid>
      <title>Unilateral dopamine deficit and lateral eeg asymmetry: sleep abnormalities in hemi-Parkinson's patients.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17707679</pmid>
      <title>The rationale for continuous dopaminergic stimulation in advanced Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17290452</pmid>
      <title>Higher nigrostriatal dopamine neuron loss in early than late onset Parkinson's disease?--a [99mTc]-TRODAT-1 SPECT study.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12846971</pmid>
      <title>PET studies on the function of dopamine in health and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2908162</pmid>
      <title>Synaptic and non-synaptic striatal dopamine D2 receptors: possible implications in normal and pathological behaviour.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7624495</pmid>
      <title>The effect of sleep deprivation on motor impairment and retinal adaptation in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2969952</pmid>
      <title>Mapping dopamine receptors in the human brain.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16260646</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors set the pattern of activity generated in subthalamic neurons.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21182589</pmid>
      <title>P25alpha / TPPP expression increases plasma membrane presentation of the dopamine transporter and enhances cellular sensitivity to dopamine toxicity.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21259269</pmid>
      <title>Cell transplantation and gene therapy in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19272288</pmid>
      <title>[The relevance of dopamine agonists in the treatment of depression].
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8531220</pmid>
      <title>GM1 ganglioside rescues substantia nigra pars compacta neurons and increases dopamine synthesis in residual nigrostriatal dopaminergic neurons in MPTP-treated mice.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11498597</pmid>
      <title>Expectation and dopamine release: mechanism of the placebo effect in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1378662</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor interactions: some implications for the treatment of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9822765</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine modulates the susceptibility of striatal neurons to 3-nitropropionic acid in the rat model of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3707090</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine denervation does not alter in vivo 3H-spiperone binding in rat striatum: implications for external imaging of dopamine receptors in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10570493</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine release from nigral transplants visualized in vivo in a Parkinson's patient.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7566450</pmid>
      <title>Alterations in dopaminergic function in Rett syndrome.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9591518</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa therapy: consequences of the nonphysiologic replacement of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11436352</pmid>
      <title>Gene therapy for Parkinson's disease: determining the genes necessary for optimal dopamine replacement in rat models.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18057916</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine transporter mutant mice in experimental neuropharmacology.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20732972</pmid>
      <title>alpha6ss2* and alpha4ss2* nicotinic receptors both regulate dopamine signaling with increased nigrostriatal damage: relevance to Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8248849</pmid>
      <title>Low density of dopamine D4 receptors in Parkinson's, schizophrenia, and control brain striata.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17017511</pmid>
      <title>Striatal plasticity in parkinsonism: dystrophic changes in medium spiny neurons and progression in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15681811</pmid>
      <title>The degeneration of dopamine neurons in Parkinson's disease: insights from embryology and evolution of the mesostriatocortical system.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10401786</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa induces a cytoplasmic localization of D1 dopamine receptors in striatal neurons in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2197154</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors and transporters in Parkinson's disease and schizophrenia.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12689773</pmid>
      <title>Presymptomatic compensation in Parkinson's disease is not dopamine-mediated.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="25">
    <article>
      <pmid>9620058</pmid>
      <title>Polymorphisms of dopamine receptor and transporter genes and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17290452</pmid>
      <title>Higher nigrostriatal dopamine neuron loss in early than late onset Parkinson's disease?--a [99mTc]-TRODAT-1 SPECT study.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6152262</pmid>
      <title>Neuropeptides in dopamine-containing regions of the brain.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18057916</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine transporter mutant mice in experimental neuropharmacology.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18781680</pmid>
      <title>Striatal and extrastriatal dopamine in the basal ganglia: an overview of its anatomical organization in normal and Parkinsonian brains.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17707679</pmid>
      <title>The rationale for continuous dopaminergic stimulation in advanced Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11436352</pmid>
      <title>Gene therapy for Parkinson's disease: determining the genes necessary for optimal dopamine replacement in rat models.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1823144</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for plasticity of the dopaminergic system in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17371292</pmid>
      <title>Movement without dopamine: striatal dopamine is required to maintain but not to perform learned actions.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20013480</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic modulation of the planning phase of skill acquisition in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2908162</pmid>
      <title>Synaptic and non-synaptic striatal dopamine D2 receptors: possible implications in normal and pathological behaviour.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1378662</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor interactions: some implications for the treatment of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9822765</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine modulates the susceptibility of striatal neurons to 3-nitropropionic acid in the rat model of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15165542</pmid>
      <title>Parkinson's disease and RLS: the dopaminergic bridge.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21182589</pmid>
      <title>P25alpha / TPPP expression increases plasma membrane presentation of the dopamine transporter and enhances cellular sensitivity to dopamine toxicity.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8531220</pmid>
      <title>GM1 ganglioside rescues substantia nigra pars compacta neurons and increases dopamine synthesis in residual nigrostriatal dopaminergic neurons in MPTP-treated mice.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20732972</pmid>
      <title>alpha6ss2* and alpha4ss2* nicotinic receptors both regulate dopamine signaling with increased nigrostriatal damage: relevance to Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7566450</pmid>
      <title>Alterations in dopaminergic function in Rett syndrome.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18325544</pmid>
      <title>Spreading activation of lexical-semantic networks in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16260646</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors set the pattern of activity generated in subthalamic neurons.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9380041</pmid>
      <title>The dopamine transporter: a crucial component regulating dopamine transmission.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11498597</pmid>
      <title>Expectation and dopamine release: mechanism of the placebo effect in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16944357</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic action beyond its effects on motor function: imaging studies.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15710494</pmid>
      <title>Impaired acquisition of skilled behavior in rotarod task by moderate depletion of striatal dopamine in a pre-symptomatic stage model of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10101608</pmid>
      <title>[Behavioral, cellular and molecular consequences of the dopamine transporter gene inactivation].
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20945978</pmid>
      <title>Imaging dopamine transporters in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21259269</pmid>
      <title>Cell transplantation and gene therapy in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>5550505</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine: stimulation-induced release from central neurons.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12846971</pmid>
      <title>PET studies on the function of dopamine in health and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20977677</pmid>
      <title>Proteomic analysis of dopamine and alpha-synuclein interplay in a cellular model of Parkinson's disease pathogenesis.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3707090</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine denervation does not alter in vivo 3H-spiperone binding in rat striatum: implications for external imaging of dopamine receptors in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19070633</pmid>
      <title>Systemic lipopolysaccharide plus MPTP as a model of dopamine loss and gait instability in C57Bl/6J mice.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>14531042</pmid>
      <title>Role of dopamine transporter imaging in the diagnosis of atypical tremor disorders.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17046697</pmid>
      <title>Rapid alterations in corticostriatal ensemble coordination during acute dopamine-dependent motor dysfunction.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="26">
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18781680</pmid>
      <title>Striatal and extrastriatal dopamine in the basal ganglia: an overview of its anatomical organization in normal and Parkinsonian brains.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9822765</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine modulates the susceptibility of striatal neurons to 3-nitropropionic acid in the rat model of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2908162</pmid>
      <title>Synaptic and non-synaptic striatal dopamine D2 receptors: possible implications in normal and pathological behaviour.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1823144</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for plasticity of the dopaminergic system in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17707679</pmid>
      <title>The rationale for continuous dopaminergic stimulation in advanced Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6152262</pmid>
      <title>Neuropeptides in dopamine-containing regions of the brain.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8531220</pmid>
      <title>GM1 ganglioside rescues substantia nigra pars compacta neurons and increases dopamine synthesis in residual nigrostriatal dopaminergic neurons in MPTP-treated mice.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18852892</pmid>
      <title>Inhibition of alpha-synuclein fibrillization by dopamine is mediated by interactions with five C-terminal residues and with E83 in the NAC region.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18325544</pmid>
      <title>Spreading activation of lexical-semantic networks in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9380041</pmid>
      <title>The dopamine transporter: a crucial component regulating dopamine transmission.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11436352</pmid>
      <title>Gene therapy for Parkinson's disease: determining the genes necessary for optimal dopamine replacement in rat models.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20732972</pmid>
      <title>alpha6ss2* and alpha4ss2* nicotinic receptors both regulate dopamine signaling with increased nigrostriatal damage: relevance to Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15189334</pmid>
      <title>Could a loss of alpha-synuclein function put dopaminergic neurons at risk?
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18039462</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine differentially induces aggregation of A53T mutant and wild type alpha-synuclein: insights into the protein chemistry of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1378662</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor interactions: some implications for the treatment of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21259269</pmid>
      <title>Cell transplantation and gene therapy in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11078922</pmid>
      <title>Cellular dopamine is increased following exposure to a factor derived from immortalized striatal neurons [corrected].
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21182589</pmid>
      <title>P25alpha / TPPP expression increases plasma membrane presentation of the dopamine transporter and enhances cellular sensitivity to dopamine toxicity.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15350965</pmid>
      <title>Synergistic effects of dopamine and Zn2+ on the induction of PC12 cell death and dopamine depletion in the striatum: possible implication in the pathogenesis of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12145295</pmid>
      <title>Effect of mutant alpha-synuclein on dopamine homeostasis in a new human mesencephalic cell line.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3707090</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine denervation does not alter in vivo 3H-spiperone binding in rat striatum: implications for external imaging of dopamine receptors in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17371292</pmid>
      <title>Movement without dopamine: striatal dopamine is required to maintain but not to perform learned actions.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19070633</pmid>
      <title>Systemic lipopolysaccharide plus MPTP as a model of dopamine loss and gait instability in C57Bl/6J mice.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20013480</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic modulation of the planning phase of skill acquisition in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9591518</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa therapy: consequences of the nonphysiologic replacement of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6254020</pmid>
      <title>Tyrosine administration increases striatal dopamine release in rats with partial nigrostriatal lesions.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17065224</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine enhances motor and neuropathological consequences of polyglutamine expanded huntingtin.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20679593</pmid>
      <title>Effects of expectation on placebo-induced dopamine release in Parkinson disease.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11498597</pmid>
      <title>Expectation and dopamine release: mechanism of the placebo effect in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>5550505</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine: stimulation-induced release from central neurons.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15710494</pmid>
      <title>Impaired acquisition of skilled behavior in rotarod task by moderate depletion of striatal dopamine in a pre-symptomatic stage model of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10401786</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa induces a cytoplasmic localization of D1 dopamine receptors in striatal neurons in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10829080</pmid>
      <title>Severe deficiencies in dopamine signaling in presymptomatic Huntington's disease mice.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10570493</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine release from nigral transplants visualized in vivo in a Parkinson's patient.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="27">
    <article>
      <pmid>9620058</pmid>
      <title>Polymorphisms of dopamine receptor and transporter genes and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17290452</pmid>
      <title>Higher nigrostriatal dopamine neuron loss in early than late onset Parkinson's disease?--a [99mTc]-TRODAT-1 SPECT study.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20945978</pmid>
      <title>Imaging dopamine transporters in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>14531042</pmid>
      <title>Role of dopamine transporter imaging in the diagnosis of atypical tremor disorders.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18057916</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine transporter mutant mice in experimental neuropharmacology.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20720060</pmid>
      <title>Molecular imaging of the dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18267275</pmid>
      <title>Positron emission tomography in premotor Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12210886</pmid>
      <title>Association between dopamine transporter gene polymorphism and susceptibility to Parkinson's disease in Japan.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1823144</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for plasticity of the dopaminergic system in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16702228</pmid>
      <title>Polychlorinated biphenyl-induced reduction of dopamine transporter expression as a precursor to Parkinson's disease-associated dopamine toxicity.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10101608</pmid>
      <title>[Behavioral, cellular and molecular consequences of the dopamine transporter gene inactivation].
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16257254</pmid>
      <title>Disease-related and drug-induced changes in dopamine transporter expression might undermine the reliability of imaging studies of disease progression in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20013480</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic modulation of the planning phase of skill acquisition in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18781680</pmid>
      <title>Striatal and extrastriatal dopamine in the basal ganglia: an overview of its anatomical organization in normal and Parkinsonian brains.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12815660</pmid>
      <title>Lack of effect of polymorphisms in dopamine metabolism related genes on imaging of TRODAT-1 in striatum of asymptomatic volunteers and patients with Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1729408</pmid>
      <title>Aging produces a specific pattern of striatal dopamine loss: implications for the etiology of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16613553</pmid>
      <title>Molecular biology, pharmacology and functional role of the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2908162</pmid>
      <title>Synaptic and non-synaptic striatal dopamine D2 receptors: possible implications in normal and pathological behaviour.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20338240</pmid>
      <title>Reduced dopamine transporter density in the ventral striatum of patients with Parkinson's disease and pathological gambling.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17886297</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine transporter relation to dopamine turnover in Parkinson's disease: a positron emission tomography study.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17119698</pmid>
      <title>Parkinson's disease and dopamine transporter neuroimaging: a critical review.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9822765</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine modulates the susceptibility of striatal neurons to 3-nitropropionic acid in the rat model of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18248965</pmid>
      <title>[99mTc]TRODAT-1/[123I]IBZM SPECT studies of the dopaminergic system in Tourette syndrome.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17119808</pmid>
      <title>[Neuroimaging of the dopamine transporter in Parkinsons disease: first study using [99mTc]-TRODAT-1 and SPECT in Brazil].
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1378662</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor interactions: some implications for the treatment of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18502656</pmid>
      <title>A voxel-based PET study of dopamine transporters in Parkinson's disease: relevance of age at onset.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11436352</pmid>
      <title>Gene therapy for Parkinson's disease: determining the genes necessary for optimal dopamine replacement in rat models.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12846971</pmid>
      <title>PET studies on the function of dopamine in health and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15130772</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine toxicity involves mitochondrial complex I inhibition: implications to dopamine-related neuropsychiatric disorders.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20809346</pmid>
      <title>Striatal dopamine function in a family with multiple SCA-3 phenotypes.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10983695</pmid>
      <title>Association of the dopamine transporter gene with Parkinson's disease in Korean patients.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15362717</pmid>
      <title>Changes of dopamine turnover in the progression of Parkinson's disease as measured by positron emission tomography: their relation to disease-compensatory mechanisms.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21259269</pmid>
      <title>Cell transplantation and gene therapy in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12422069</pmid>
      <title>Association study for Parkinson's disease and a dopamine transporter gene polymorphism (1215A/G).
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17707679</pmid>
      <title>The rationale for continuous dopaminergic stimulation in advanced Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17046697</pmid>
      <title>Rapid alterations in corticostriatal ensemble coordination during acute dopamine-dependent motor dysfunction.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="28">
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1823144</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for plasticity of the dopaminergic system in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15130772</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine toxicity involves mitochondrial complex I inhibition: implications to dopamine-related neuropsychiatric disorders.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20013480</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic modulation of the planning phase of skill acquisition in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>14531040</pmid>
      <title>Role of dopamine transporter SPECT for the practitioner and the general neurologist.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11436352</pmid>
      <title>Gene therapy for Parkinson's disease: determining the genes necessary for optimal dopamine replacement in rat models.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8531220</pmid>
      <title>GM1 ganglioside rescues substantia nigra pars compacta neurons and increases dopamine synthesis in residual nigrostriatal dopaminergic neurons in MPTP-treated mice.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18781680</pmid>
      <title>Striatal and extrastriatal dopamine in the basal ganglia: an overview of its anatomical organization in normal and Parkinsonian brains.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>5550505</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine: stimulation-induced release from central neurons.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2908162</pmid>
      <title>Synaptic and non-synaptic striatal dopamine D2 receptors: possible implications in normal and pathological behaviour.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17371292</pmid>
      <title>Movement without dopamine: striatal dopamine is required to maintain but not to perform learned actions.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1378662</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor interactions: some implications for the treatment of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12460681</pmid>
      <title>Mitochondrial damage by nitric oxide is potentiated by dopamine in PC12 cells.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19070633</pmid>
      <title>Systemic lipopolysaccharide plus MPTP as a model of dopamine loss and gait instability in C57Bl/6J mice.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21259269</pmid>
      <title>Cell transplantation and gene therapy in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20679593</pmid>
      <title>Effects of expectation on placebo-induced dopamine release in Parkinson disease.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20977677</pmid>
      <title>Proteomic analysis of dopamine and alpha-synuclein interplay in a cellular model of Parkinson's disease pathogenesis.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6420835</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine/L-dopa ratio in cerebrospinal fluid of parkinsonian patients treated with L-dopa + benserazide.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20368163</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine gene therapy for Parkinson's disease in a nonhuman primate without associated dyskinesia.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9822765</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine modulates the susceptibility of striatal neurons to 3-nitropropionic acid in the rat model of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15350965</pmid>
      <title>Synergistic effects of dopamine and Zn2+ on the induction of PC12 cell death and dopamine depletion in the striatum: possible implication in the pathogenesis of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17707679</pmid>
      <title>The rationale for continuous dopaminergic stimulation in advanced Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6540390</pmid>
      <title>Altered pharmacokinetics of L-dopa metabolism in rat striatum deprived of dopaminergic innervation.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21781190</pmid>
      <title>Evaluating dopaminergic system contributions to cued pattern switching during bimanual coordination.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11052227</pmid>
      <title>PET studies and motor complications in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19516251</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine modulates cholinergic cortical excitability in Alzheimer's disease patients.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20732972</pmid>
      <title>alpha6ss2* and alpha4ss2* nicotinic receptors both regulate dopamine signaling with increased nigrostriatal damage: relevance to Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8904076</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa biotransformation in hemi-Parkinson rats: effect of dopamine receptor agonists and antagonists.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9380041</pmid>
      <title>The dopamine transporter: a crucial component regulating dopamine transmission.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8104554</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor pharmacology.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11078922</pmid>
      <title>Cellular dopamine is increased following exposure to a factor derived from immortalized striatal neurons [corrected].
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15790526</pmid>
      <title>Synuclein, dopamine and oxidative stress: co-conspirators in Parkinson's disease?
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12689773</pmid>
      <title>Presymptomatic compensation in Parkinson's disease is not dopamine-mediated.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16356326</pmid>
      <title>An effect of dopamine depletion on decision-making: the temporal coupling of deliberation and execution.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19362126</pmid>
      <title>In vivo dopamine release and uptake impairments in rats treated with 3-nitropropionic acid.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7902865</pmid>
      <title>Regulation of dopamine production by genetically modified primary fibroblasts.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7754301</pmid>
      <title>Behavior-related activity of primate dopamine neurons.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15710494</pmid>
      <title>Impaired acquisition of skilled behavior in rotarod task by moderate depletion of striatal dopamine in a pre-symptomatic stage model of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16944357</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic action beyond its effects on motor function: imaging studies.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9886073</pmid>
      <title>Influence of age and strain on striatal dopamine loss in a genetic mouse model of Lesch-Nyhan disease.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="31">
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1378662</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor interactions: some implications for the treatment of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15130772</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine toxicity involves mitochondrial complex I inhibition: implications to dopamine-related neuropsychiatric disorders.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11436352</pmid>
      <title>Gene therapy for Parkinson's disease: determining the genes necessary for optimal dopamine replacement in rat models.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1823144</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for plasticity of the dopaminergic system in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2197154</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors and transporters in Parkinson's disease and schizophrenia.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6152262</pmid>
      <title>Neuropeptides in dopamine-containing regions of the brain.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2908162</pmid>
      <title>Synaptic and non-synaptic striatal dopamine D2 receptors: possible implications in normal and pathological behaviour.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15362717</pmid>
      <title>Changes of dopamine turnover in the progression of Parkinson's disease as measured by positron emission tomography: their relation to disease-compensatory mechanisms.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>5550505</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine: stimulation-induced release from central neurons.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18322366</pmid>
      <title>Basic research on dopamine in Parkinson's disease and the discovery of the nigrostriatal dopamine pathway: the view of an eyewitness.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18325544</pmid>
      <title>Spreading activation of lexical-semantic networks in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12846971</pmid>
      <title>PET studies on the function of dopamine in health and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6540390</pmid>
      <title>Altered pharmacokinetics of L-dopa metabolism in rat striatum deprived of dopaminergic innervation.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1729408</pmid>
      <title>Aging produces a specific pattern of striatal dopamine loss: implications for the etiology of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8531220</pmid>
      <title>GM1 ganglioside rescues substantia nigra pars compacta neurons and increases dopamine synthesis in residual nigrostriatal dopaminergic neurons in MPTP-treated mice.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20977677</pmid>
      <title>Proteomic analysis of dopamine and alpha-synuclein interplay in a cellular model of Parkinson's disease pathogenesis.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21259269</pmid>
      <title>Cell transplantation and gene therapy in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16944357</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic action beyond its effects on motor function: imaging studies.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1772579</pmid>
      <title>A study of brain dopamine sulfate levels in relation to free dopamine and homovanillic acid in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11498597</pmid>
      <title>Expectation and dopamine release: mechanism of the placebo effect in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20732972</pmid>
      <title>alpha6ss2* and alpha4ss2* nicotinic receptors both regulate dopamine signaling with increased nigrostriatal damage: relevance to Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9380041</pmid>
      <title>The dopamine transporter: a crucial component regulating dopamine transmission.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2969952</pmid>
      <title>Mapping dopamine receptors in the human brain.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19070633</pmid>
      <title>Systemic lipopolysaccharide plus MPTP as a model of dopamine loss and gait instability in C57Bl/6J mice.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7902865</pmid>
      <title>Regulation of dopamine production by genetically modified primary fibroblasts.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20082987</pmid>
      <title>The MitoPark Mouse - an animal model of Parkinson's disease with impaired respiratory chain function in dopamine neurons.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11052228</pmid>
      <title>Continuous dopamine-receptor stimulation in advanced Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8904076</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa biotransformation in hemi-Parkinson rats: effect of dopamine receptor agonists and antagonists.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9380062</pmid>
      <title>Association of a polymorphism in the dopamine-transporter gene with Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6504335</pmid>
      <title>Pharmacologic effects of L-dopa are not closely linked temporally to striatal dopamine concentration.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6420835</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine/L-dopa ratio in cerebrospinal fluid of parkinsonian patients treated with L-dopa + benserazide.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10661519</pmid>
      <title>Loss of dopamine uptake sites and dopamine D2 receptors in striatonigral degeneration.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12470690</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging studies of dopamine system and cognition in normal aging and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2138080</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine uptake sites and dopamine receptors in Parkinson's disease and schizophrenia.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8714754</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors--the present state of research and perspectives.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="32">
    <article>
      <pmid>15790526</pmid>
      <title>Synuclein, dopamine and oxidative stress: co-conspirators in Parkinson's disease?
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15580550</pmid>
      <title>Challenging conventional wisdom: the etiologic role of dopamine oxidative stress in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18500384</pmid>
      <title>Iron contributes to the formation of catechol isoquinolines and oxidative toxicity induced by overdose dopamine in dopaminergic SH-SY5Y cells.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20926973</pmid>
      <title>Intense dopamine innervation of the subventricular zone in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10838590</pmid>
      <title>Neuronal cell death in Huntington's disease: a potential role for dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1729408</pmid>
      <title>Aging produces a specific pattern of striatal dopamine loss: implications for the etiology of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21256185</pmid>
      <title>Impaired dopamine release and uptake in R6/1 Huntington's disease model mice.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12470690</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging studies of dopamine system and cognition in normal aging and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16573654</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine release is severely compromised in the R6/2 mouse model of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1363335</pmid>
      <title>Neuroleptic treatment is an unlikely cause of elevated dopamine in thalamus of schizophrenic subjects.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17017502</pmid>
      <title>The discovery of dopamine deficiency in the parkinsonian brain.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2197154</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors and transporters in Parkinson's disease and schizophrenia.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18322366</pmid>
      <title>Basic research on dopamine in Parkinson's disease and the discovery of the nigrostriatal dopamine pathway: the view of an eyewitness.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2445259</pmid>
      <title>Elevated serotonin and reduced dopamine in subregionally divided Huntington's disease striatum.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12690667</pmid>
      <title>[Fluctuations].
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8172940</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine D1 receptor number--a sensitive PET marker for early brain degeneration in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7566450</pmid>
      <title>Alterations in dopaminergic function in Rett syndrome.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10220107</pmid>
      <title>Cytotoxic and genotoxic potential of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6152262</pmid>
      <title>Neuropeptides in dopamine-containing regions of the brain.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1378662</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor interactions: some implications for the treatment of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20886576</pmid>
      <title>Extrastriatal dopamine D(2) receptor binding in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1772579</pmid>
      <title>A study of brain dopamine sulfate levels in relation to free dopamine and homovanillic acid in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15362717</pmid>
      <title>Changes of dopamine turnover in the progression of Parkinson's disease as measured by positron emission tomography: their relation to disease-compensatory mechanisms.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9822765</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine modulates the susceptibility of striatal neurons to 3-nitropropionic acid in the rat model of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8687191</pmid>
      <title>Striatal D1 and D2 dopamine receptor loss in asymptomatic mutation carriers of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12739402</pmid>
      <title>[Free radicals and ailing proteins--the culprits behind Parkinson disease?].
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16944357</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic action beyond its effects on motor function: imaging studies.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3653699</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine action and disorders of neurotransmitter balance.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8093582</pmid>
      <title>Recent advances in pharmacological therapy of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11052227</pmid>
      <title>PET studies and motor complications in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12706913</pmid>
      <title>Parkinsonian speech disfluencies: effects of L-dopa-related fluctuations.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1823144</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for plasticity of the dopaminergic system in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16278233</pmid>
      <title>Stress-induced alterations in parkin solubility promote parkin aggregation and compromise parkin's protective function.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18596830</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic neuron-specific oxidative stress caused by dopamine itself.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2969952</pmid>
      <title>Mapping dopamine receptors in the human brain.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11229358</pmid>
      <title>The roles of dopamine oxidative stress and dopamine receptor signaling in aging and age-related neurodegeneration.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11436352</pmid>
      <title>Gene therapy for Parkinson's disease: determining the genes necessary for optimal dopamine replacement in rat models.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15978181</pmid>
      <title>Pramipexole has ameliorating effects on levodopa-induced abnormal dopamine turnover in parkinsonian striatum and quenching effects on dopamine-semiquinone generated in vitro.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="44">
    <article>
      <pmid>12207999</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and the representation of the upper visual field: evidence from vertical bisection errors in unilateral Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18039462</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine differentially induces aggregation of A53T mutant and wild type alpha-synuclein: insights into the protein chemistry of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19896832</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and synaptic plasticity in dorsal striatal circuits controlling action selection.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17682727</pmid>
      <title>Changes of dopamine receptors in mice with olivocerebellar degeneration.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12689773</pmid>
      <title>Presymptomatic compensation in Parkinson's disease is not dopamine-mediated.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6152262</pmid>
      <title>Neuropeptides in dopamine-containing regions of the brain.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16944357</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic action beyond its effects on motor function: imaging studies.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15710494</pmid>
      <title>Impaired acquisition of skilled behavior in rotarod task by moderate depletion of striatal dopamine in a pre-symptomatic stage model of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7566450</pmid>
      <title>Alterations in dopaminergic function in Rett syndrome.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7754301</pmid>
      <title>Behavior-related activity of primate dopamine neurons.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17371292</pmid>
      <title>Movement without dopamine: striatal dopamine is required to maintain but not to perform learned actions.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12690667</pmid>
      <title>[Fluctuations].
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15130772</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine toxicity involves mitochondrial complex I inhibition: implications to dopamine-related neuropsychiatric disorders.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19070633</pmid>
      <title>Systemic lipopolysaccharide plus MPTP as a model of dopamine loss and gait instability in C57Bl/6J mice.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17065224</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine enhances motor and neuropathological consequences of polyglutamine expanded huntingtin.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20977677</pmid>
      <title>Proteomic analysis of dopamine and alpha-synuclein interplay in a cellular model of Parkinson's disease pathogenesis.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7509865</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in a genetic mouse model of Lesch-Nyhan disease.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18325544</pmid>
      <title>Spreading activation of lexical-semantic networks in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11078922</pmid>
      <title>Cellular dopamine is increased following exposure to a factor derived from immortalized striatal neurons [corrected].
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16876208</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine asymmetry interacts with medication to affect cognition in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1838678</pmid>
      <title>Abnormal dopamine uptake sites in postmortem striatum from patients with Tourette's syndrome.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20013480</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic modulation of the planning phase of skill acquisition in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3024663</pmid>
      <title>An examination of parkinsonian versus anhedonia contributions to self-stimulation impairments induced by dopamine dysfunction.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19682583</pmid>
      <title>Selective impairment of prediction error signaling in human dorsolateral but not ventral striatum in Parkinson's disease patients: evidence from a model-based fMRI study.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1801100</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse: an animal model of olivopontocerebellar atrophy.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20044893</pmid>
      <title>A neurocomputational model of dopamine and prefrontal-striatal interactions during multicue category learning by Parkinson patients.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21259269</pmid>
      <title>Cell transplantation and gene therapy in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18348679</pmid>
      <title>Potential therapeutic targets for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18313759</pmid>
      <title>Genetic factors involved in the pathogenesis of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12460681</pmid>
      <title>Mitochondrial damage by nitric oxide is potentiated by dopamine in PC12 cells.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9771125</pmid>
      <title>[Functional role and pharmacological regulation of the dopaminergic system of the brain].
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12145295</pmid>
      <title>Effect of mutant alpha-synuclein on dopamine homeostasis in a new human mesencephalic cell line.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3707090</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine denervation does not alter in vivo 3H-spiperone binding in rat striatum: implications for external imaging of dopamine receptors in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11498597</pmid>
      <title>Expectation and dopamine release: mechanism of the placebo effect in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16613557</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and the diseased brain.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1772579</pmid>
      <title>A study of brain dopamine sulfate levels in relation to free dopamine and homovanillic acid in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="46">
    <article>
      <pmid>18039462</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine differentially induces aggregation of A53T mutant and wild type alpha-synuclein: insights into the protein chemistry of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15790526</pmid>
      <title>Synuclein, dopamine and oxidative stress: co-conspirators in Parkinson's disease?
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12846971</pmid>
      <title>PET studies on the function of dopamine in health and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3653699</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine action and disorders of neurotransmitter balance.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17046697</pmid>
      <title>Rapid alterations in corticostriatal ensemble coordination during acute dopamine-dependent motor dysfunction.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12145295</pmid>
      <title>Effect of mutant alpha-synuclein on dopamine homeostasis in a new human mesencephalic cell line.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17065224</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine enhances motor and neuropathological consequences of polyglutamine expanded huntingtin.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11498597</pmid>
      <title>Expectation and dopamine release: mechanism of the placebo effect in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18325544</pmid>
      <title>Spreading activation of lexical-semantic networks in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9380062</pmid>
      <title>Association of a polymorphism in the dopamine-transporter gene with Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6152262</pmid>
      <title>Neuropeptides in dopamine-containing regions of the brain.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16944357</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic action beyond its effects on motor function: imaging studies.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20013480</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic modulation of the planning phase of skill acquisition in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1510367</pmid>
      <title>Role of iron and iron chelation in dopaminergic-induced neurodegeneration: implication for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18852892</pmid>
      <title>Inhibition of alpha-synuclein fibrillization by dopamine is mediated by interactions with five C-terminal residues and with E83 in the NAC region.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17371292</pmid>
      <title>Movement without dopamine: striatal dopamine is required to maintain but not to perform learned actions.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20732972</pmid>
      <title>alpha6ss2* and alpha4ss2* nicotinic receptors both regulate dopamine signaling with increased nigrostriatal damage: relevance to Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1729408</pmid>
      <title>Aging produces a specific pattern of striatal dopamine loss: implications for the etiology of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15580550</pmid>
      <title>Challenging conventional wisdom: the etiologic role of dopamine oxidative stress in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20977677</pmid>
      <title>Proteomic analysis of dopamine and alpha-synuclein interplay in a cellular model of Parkinson's disease pathogenesis.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1296037</pmid>
      <title>The serum ferrokinetics in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9380041</pmid>
      <title>The dopamine transporter: a crucial component regulating dopamine transmission.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8099797</pmid>
      <title>Prefrontal cortical dopamine systems and the elaboration of functional corticostriatal circuits: implications for schizophrenia and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19896832</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and synaptic plasticity in dorsal striatal circuits controlling action selection.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7509865</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in a genetic mouse model of Lesch-Nyhan disease.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15822108</pmid>
      <title>Pathophysiology of motor fluctuations in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15350965</pmid>
      <title>Synergistic effects of dopamine and Zn2+ on the induction of PC12 cell death and dopamine depletion in the striatum: possible implication in the pathogenesis of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17868972</pmid>
      <title>Incentive motivation is associated with striatal dopamine asymmetry.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20145921</pmid>
      <title>SPECT neuroimaging and neuropsychological functions in different stages of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1801100</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse: an animal model of olivopontocerebellar atrophy.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21182589</pmid>
      <title>P25alpha / TPPP expression increases plasma membrane presentation of the dopamine transporter and enhances cellular sensitivity to dopamine toxicity.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20334701</pmid>
      <title>Alpha-synuclein overexpression increases dopamine toxicity in BE2-M17 cells.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068438</pmid>
      <title>[SPECT and PET in Parkinson's disease].
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9822765</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine modulates the susceptibility of striatal neurons to 3-nitropropionic acid in the rat model of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="51">
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15582105</pmid>
      <title>The role of dopamine in cognitive sequence learning: evidence from Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1729408</pmid>
      <title>Aging produces a specific pattern of striatal dopamine loss: implications for the etiology of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15528409</pmid>
      <title>By carrot or by stick: cognitive reinforcement learning in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11498597</pmid>
      <title>Expectation and dopamine release: mechanism of the placebo effect in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17707679</pmid>
      <title>The rationale for continuous dopaminergic stimulation in advanced Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20013480</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic modulation of the planning phase of skill acquisition in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6152262</pmid>
      <title>Neuropeptides in dopamine-containing regions of the brain.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18325544</pmid>
      <title>Spreading activation of lexical-semantic networks in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19896832</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and synaptic plasticity in dorsal striatal circuits controlling action selection.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19628022</pmid>
      <title>Probabilistic reversal learning is impaired in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12846971</pmid>
      <title>PET studies on the function of dopamine in health and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9380062</pmid>
      <title>Association of a polymorphism in the dopamine-transporter gene with Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3707090</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine denervation does not alter in vivo 3H-spiperone binding in rat striatum: implications for external imaging of dopamine receptors in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18781680</pmid>
      <title>Striatal and extrastriatal dopamine in the basal ganglia: an overview of its anatomical organization in normal and Parkinsonian brains.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9822765</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine modulates the susceptibility of striatal neurons to 3-nitropropionic acid in the rat model of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12756643</pmid>
      <title>Imaging studies in movement disorders.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20732972</pmid>
      <title>alpha6ss2* and alpha4ss2* nicotinic receptors both regulate dopamine signaling with increased nigrostriatal damage: relevance to Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21182589</pmid>
      <title>P25alpha / TPPP expression increases plasma membrane presentation of the dopamine transporter and enhances cellular sensitivity to dopamine toxicity.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19070633</pmid>
      <title>Systemic lipopolysaccharide plus MPTP as a model of dopamine loss and gait instability in C57Bl/6J mice.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8714754</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors--the present state of research and perspectives.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10570493</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine release from nigral transplants visualized in vivo in a Parkinson's patient.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16260646</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors set the pattern of activity generated in subthalamic neurons.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15350965</pmid>
      <title>Synergistic effects of dopamine and Zn2+ on the induction of PC12 cell death and dopamine depletion in the striatum: possible implication in the pathogenesis of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21256185</pmid>
      <title>Impaired dopamine release and uptake in R6/1 Huntington's disease model mice.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1838678</pmid>
      <title>Abnormal dopamine uptake sites in postmortem striatum from patients with Tourette's syndrome.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21259269</pmid>
      <title>Cell transplantation and gene therapy in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2969952</pmid>
      <title>Mapping dopamine receptors in the human brain.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1772579</pmid>
      <title>A study of brain dopamine sulfate levels in relation to free dopamine and homovanillic acid in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12538400</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine release during sequential finger movements in health and Parkinson's disease: a PET study.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7509865</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in a genetic mouse model of Lesch-Nyhan disease.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20044893</pmid>
      <title>A neurocomputational model of dopamine and prefrontal-striatal interactions during multicue category learning by Parkinson patients.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19061540</pmid>
      <title>Central and peripheral dopamine transporter reduction in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9380041</pmid>
      <title>The dopamine transporter: a crucial component regulating dopamine transmission.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="55">
    <article>
      <pmid>15790526</pmid>
      <title>Synuclein, dopamine and oxidative stress: co-conspirators in Parkinson's disease?
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6152262</pmid>
      <title>Neuropeptides in dopamine-containing regions of the brain.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15580550</pmid>
      <title>Challenging conventional wisdom: the etiologic role of dopamine oxidative stress in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12778453</pmid>
      <title>[Dopamine beta hydroxylase gene polymorphism and Parkinson's disease].
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17017502</pmid>
      <title>The discovery of dopamine deficiency in the parkinsonian brain.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10762168</pmid>
      <title>A single nucleotide polymorphism of dopamine transporter gene is associated with Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2969952</pmid>
      <title>Mapping dopamine receptors in the human brain.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11445276</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine D5 receptor gene polymorphism and the risk of levodopa-induced motor fluctuations in patients with Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1772579</pmid>
      <title>A study of brain dopamine sulfate levels in relation to free dopamine and homovanillic acid in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20013480</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic modulation of the planning phase of skill acquisition in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11104188</pmid>
      <title>Allelic association between the DRD2 TaqI A polymorphism and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18322366</pmid>
      <title>Basic research on dopamine in Parkinson's disease and the discovery of the nigrostriatal dopamine pathway: the view of an eyewitness.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12690667</pmid>
      <title>[Fluctuations].
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17707679</pmid>
      <title>The rationale for continuous dopaminergic stimulation in advanced Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11425949</pmid>
      <title>Association study of dopamine D2, D3 receptor gene polymorphisms with motor fluctuations in PD.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>14991826</pmid>
      <title>A functional polymorphism regulating dopamine beta-hydroxylase influences against Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7810582</pmid>
      <title>Association analysis of the dopamine D2 receptor gene in Tourette's syndrome using the haplotype relative risk method.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16356326</pmid>
      <title>An effect of dopamine depletion on decision-making: the temporal coupling of deliberation and execution.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18325544</pmid>
      <title>Spreading activation of lexical-semantic networks in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12351575</pmid>
      <title>Impaired dopamine storage resulting from alpha-synuclein mutations may contribute to the pathogenesis of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15297154</pmid>
      <title>Genetic contributions to Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10634251</pmid>
      <title>The dopamine D2 receptor gene is a susceptibility locus for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8099797</pmid>
      <title>Prefrontal cortical dopamine systems and the elaboration of functional corticostriatal circuits: implications for schizophrenia and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15978181</pmid>
      <title>Pramipexole has ameliorating effects on levodopa-induced abnormal dopamine turnover in parkinsonian striatum and quenching effects on dopamine-semiquinone generated in vitro.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1729408</pmid>
      <title>Aging produces a specific pattern of striatal dopamine loss: implications for the etiology of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18327668</pmid>
      <title>Polymorphism in environment responsive genes and association with Parkinson disease.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15198987</pmid>
      <title>Parkin protects human dopaminergic neuroblastoma cells against dopamine-induced apoptosis.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12756643</pmid>
      <title>Imaging studies in movement disorders.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9409349</pmid>
      <title>The dopamine transporter gene and Parkinson's disease in a Chinese population.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16260646</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors set the pattern of activity generated in subthalamic neurons.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3707090</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine denervation does not alter in vivo 3H-spiperone binding in rat striatum: implications for external imaging of dopamine receptors in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8714754</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors--the present state of research and perspectives.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20886576</pmid>
      <title>Extrastriatal dopamine D(2) receptor binding in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8248849</pmid>
      <title>Low density of dopamine D4 receptors in Parkinson's, schizophrenia, and control brain striata.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21259269</pmid>
      <title>Cell transplantation and gene therapy in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="73">
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15130772</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine toxicity involves mitochondrial complex I inhibition: implications to dopamine-related neuropsychiatric disorders.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12706913</pmid>
      <title>Parkinsonian speech disfluencies: effects of L-dopa-related fluctuations.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20977677</pmid>
      <title>Proteomic analysis of dopamine and alpha-synuclein interplay in a cellular model of Parkinson's disease pathogenesis.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1729408</pmid>
      <title>Aging produces a specific pattern of striatal dopamine loss: implications for the etiology of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8714754</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors--the present state of research and perspectives.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17017511</pmid>
      <title>Striatal plasticity in parkinsonism: dystrophic changes in medium spiny neurons and progression in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17575584</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine levels after repetitive transcranial magnetic stimulation of motor cortex in patients with Parkinson's disease: preliminary results.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930746</pmid>
      <title>CNS compensation to dopamine neuron loss in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16944357</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic action beyond its effects on motor function: imaging studies.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12846971</pmid>
      <title>PET studies on the function of dopamine in health and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8104554</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor pharmacology.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9620058</pmid>
      <title>Polymorphisms of dopamine receptor and transporter genes and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1772579</pmid>
      <title>A study of brain dopamine sulfate levels in relation to free dopamine and homovanillic acid in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19070633</pmid>
      <title>Systemic lipopolysaccharide plus MPTP as a model of dopamine loss and gait instability in C57Bl/6J mice.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10762131</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-mediated gene regulation in models of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17046697</pmid>
      <title>Rapid alterations in corticostriatal ensemble coordination during acute dopamine-dependent motor dysfunction.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19896832</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and synaptic plasticity in dorsal striatal circuits controlling action selection.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3165432</pmid>
      <title>Continuous intracerebroventricular infusion of dopamine and dopamine agonists through a totally implanted drug delivery system in animal models of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2969952</pmid>
      <title>Mapping dopamine receptors in the human brain.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16243049</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine dependency of cognitive switching and response repetition effects in Parkinson's patients.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10570493</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine release from nigral transplants visualized in vivo in a Parkinson's patient.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8248849</pmid>
      <title>Low density of dopamine D4 receptors in Parkinson's, schizophrenia, and control brain striata.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11498597</pmid>
      <title>Expectation and dopamine release: mechanism of the placebo effect in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9349549</pmid>
      <title>In vivo electrochemical measurement of the long-lasting release of dopamine and serotonin induced by intrastriatal kainic acid.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21474106</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine controls neurogenesis in the adult salamander midbrain in homeostasis and during regeneration of dopamine neurons.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9886073</pmid>
      <title>Influence of age and strain on striatal dopamine loss in a genetic mouse model of Lesch-Nyhan disease.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11436352</pmid>
      <title>Gene therapy for Parkinson's disease: determining the genes necessary for optimal dopamine replacement in rat models.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3549845</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and serotonin systems in human and rodent brain: effects of age and neurodegenerative disease.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10101608</pmid>
      <title>[Behavioral, cellular and molecular consequences of the dopamine transporter gene inactivation].
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9822765</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine modulates the susceptibility of striatal neurons to 3-nitropropionic acid in the rat model of Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11514985</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for target-specific outgrowth from subpopulations of grafted human dopamine neurons.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15710494</pmid>
      <title>Impaired acquisition of skilled behavior in rotarod task by moderate depletion of striatal dopamine in a pre-symptomatic stage model of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10401786</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa induces a cytoplasmic localization of D1 dopamine receptors in striatal neurons in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="74">
    <article>
      <pmid>12706913</pmid>
      <title>Parkinsonian speech disfluencies: effects of L-dopa-related fluctuations.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11498597</pmid>
      <title>Expectation and dopamine release: mechanism of the placebo effect in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7509865</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in a genetic mouse model of Lesch-Nyhan disease.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20977677</pmid>
      <title>Proteomic analysis of dopamine and alpha-synuclein interplay in a cellular model of Parkinson's disease pathogenesis.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17065224</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine enhances motor and neuropathological consequences of polyglutamine expanded huntingtin.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2969952</pmid>
      <title>Mapping dopamine receptors in the human brain.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1729408</pmid>
      <title>Aging produces a specific pattern of striatal dopamine loss: implications for the etiology of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8714754</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors--the present state of research and perspectives.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19061540</pmid>
      <title>Central and peripheral dopamine transporter reduction in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3707090</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine denervation does not alter in vivo 3H-spiperone binding in rat striatum: implications for external imaging of dopamine receptors in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19391152</pmid>
      <title>Visualizing vesicular dopamine dynamics in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11261503</pmid>
      <title>Biochemical variations in the synaptic level of dopamine precede motor fluctuations in Parkinson's disease: PET evidence of increased dopamine turnover.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8248849</pmid>
      <title>Low density of dopamine D4 receptors in Parkinson's, schizophrenia, and control brain striata.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15130772</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine toxicity involves mitochondrial complex I inhibition: implications to dopamine-related neuropsychiatric disorders.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16243049</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine dependency of cognitive switching and response repetition effects in Parkinson's patients.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9886073</pmid>
      <title>Influence of age and strain on striatal dopamine loss in a genetic mouse model of Lesch-Nyhan disease.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2243012</pmid>
      <title>Decreased dopamine in the retinas of patients with Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1772579</pmid>
      <title>A study of brain dopamine sulfate levels in relation to free dopamine and homovanillic acid in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16324129</pmid>
      <title>Corticostriatal functional interactions in Parkinson's disease: a rTMS/[11C]raclopride PET study.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19896832</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and synaptic plasticity in dorsal striatal circuits controlling action selection.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21182589</pmid>
      <title>P25alpha / TPPP expression increases plasma membrane presentation of the dopamine transporter and enhances cellular sensitivity to dopamine toxicity.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12846971</pmid>
      <title>PET studies on the function of dopamine in health and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9620058</pmid>
      <title>Polymorphisms of dopamine receptor and transporter genes and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12145295</pmid>
      <title>Effect of mutant alpha-synuclein on dopamine homeostasis in a new human mesencephalic cell line.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17575584</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine levels after repetitive transcranial magnetic stimulation of motor cortex in patients with Parkinson's disease: preliminary results.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18039462</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine differentially induces aggregation of A53T mutant and wild type alpha-synuclein: insights into the protein chemistry of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19356748</pmid>
      <title>Semantic activation in Parkinson's disease patients on and off levodopa.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20886576</pmid>
      <title>Extrastriatal dopamine D(2) receptor binding in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19070633</pmid>
      <title>Systemic lipopolysaccharide plus MPTP as a model of dopamine loss and gait instability in C57Bl/6J mice.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17290452</pmid>
      <title>Higher nigrostriatal dopamine neuron loss in early than late onset Parkinson's disease?--a [99mTc]-TRODAT-1 SPECT study.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1823144</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for plasticity of the dopaminergic system in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16944357</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic action beyond its effects on motor function: imaging studies.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1801100</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse: an animal model of olivopontocerebellar atrophy.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="75">
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11052218</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors: from structure to behavior.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9380041</pmid>
      <title>The dopamine transporter: a crucial component regulating dopamine transmission.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8104554</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor pharmacology.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10762128</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors and locomotor responses: molecular aspects.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20977677</pmid>
      <title>Proteomic analysis of dopamine and alpha-synuclein interplay in a cellular model of Parkinson's disease pathogenesis.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3165432</pmid>
      <title>Continuous intracerebroventricular infusion of dopamine and dopamine agonists through a totally implanted drug delivery system in animal models of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17380778</pmid>
      <title>[Placebo effect in Parkinson's disease].
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17315755</pmid>
      <title>[Placebo effect in Parkinson's disease].
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10377729</pmid>
      <title>[New pharmacologic strategies for the treatment of Parkinson disease].
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8714754</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors--the present state of research and perspectives.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1801100</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse: an animal model of olivopontocerebellar atrophy.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12145295</pmid>
      <title>Effect of mutant alpha-synuclein on dopamine homeostasis in a new human mesencephalic cell line.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>14870689</pmid>
      <title>[A comparative study of efficacy of dopamine receptors agonists and catechol-O-methyltransferase in the treatment of late stages of Parkinson's disease].
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8544935</pmid>
      <title>[The role of enzymatic systems in pathophysiology and pharmacotherapy of Parkinson's disease].
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15130772</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine toxicity involves mitochondrial complex I inhibition: implications to dopamine-related neuropsychiatric disorders.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10895245</pmid>
      <title>Treatment of parkinsonian syndromes in developing countries.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1729408</pmid>
      <title>Aging produces a specific pattern of striatal dopamine loss: implications for the etiology of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17017511</pmid>
      <title>Striatal plasticity in parkinsonism: dystrophic changes in medium spiny neurons and progression in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1772579</pmid>
      <title>A study of brain dopamine sulfate levels in relation to free dopamine and homovanillic acid in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7509865</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in a genetic mouse model of Lesch-Nyhan disease.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20732972</pmid>
      <title>alpha6ss2* and alpha4ss2* nicotinic receptors both regulate dopamine signaling with increased nigrostriatal damage: relevance to Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17352343</pmid>
      <title>Canadian Association of Neurosciences Review: the role of dopamine receptor function in neurodegenerative diseases.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2969952</pmid>
      <title>Mapping dopamine receptors in the human brain.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15710494</pmid>
      <title>Impaired acquisition of skilled behavior in rotarod task by moderate depletion of striatal dopamine in a pre-symptomatic stage model of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9620058</pmid>
      <title>Polymorphisms of dopamine receptor and transporter genes and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10762131</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-mediated gene regulation in models of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16243049</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine dependency of cognitive switching and response repetition effects in Parkinson's patients.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19362126</pmid>
      <title>In vivo dopamine release and uptake impairments in rats treated with 3-nitropropionic acid.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19070633</pmid>
      <title>Systemic lipopolysaccharide plus MPTP as a model of dopamine loss and gait instability in C57Bl/6J mice.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11498597</pmid>
      <title>Expectation and dopamine release: mechanism of the placebo effect in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9886073</pmid>
      <title>Influence of age and strain on striatal dopamine loss in a genetic mouse model of Lesch-Nyhan disease.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10570493</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine release from nigral transplants visualized in vivo in a Parkinson's patient.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9349549</pmid>
      <title>In vivo electrochemical measurement of the long-lasting release of dopamine and serotonin induced by intrastriatal kainic acid.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="76">
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15710494</pmid>
      <title>Impaired acquisition of skilled behavior in rotarod task by moderate depletion of striatal dopamine in a pre-symptomatic stage model of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2881341</pmid>
      <title>Neuropharmacology of tics.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20977677</pmid>
      <title>Proteomic analysis of dopamine and alpha-synuclein interplay in a cellular model of Parkinson's disease pathogenesis.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11498597</pmid>
      <title>Expectation and dopamine release: mechanism of the placebo effect in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12846971</pmid>
      <title>PET studies on the function of dopamine in health and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1729408</pmid>
      <title>Aging produces a specific pattern of striatal dopamine loss: implications for the etiology of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16944352</pmid>
      <title>Early diagnosis of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1772579</pmid>
      <title>A study of brain dopamine sulfate levels in relation to free dopamine and homovanillic acid in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11261503</pmid>
      <title>Biochemical variations in the synaptic level of dopamine precede motor fluctuations in Parkinson's disease: PET evidence of increased dopamine turnover.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17575584</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine levels after repetitive transcranial magnetic stimulation of motor cortex in patients with Parkinson's disease: preliminary results.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15911797</pmid>
      <title>[99mTc]TRODAT-1 SPECT imaging correlates with odor identification in early Parkinson disease.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17017511</pmid>
      <title>Striatal plasticity in parkinsonism: dystrophic changes in medium spiny neurons and progression in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21256185</pmid>
      <title>Impaired dopamine release and uptake in R6/1 Huntington's disease model mice.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19362126</pmid>
      <title>In vivo dopamine release and uptake impairments in rats treated with 3-nitropropionic acid.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10570493</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine release from nigral transplants visualized in vivo in a Parkinson's patient.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10549795</pmid>
      <title>Reduced dopamine in peripheral blood lymphocytes in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19131045</pmid>
      <title>Neuroimaging of L-dopamine and dopamine agonist therapy - revisited.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8714754</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors--the present state of research and perspectives.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2969952</pmid>
      <title>Mapping dopamine receptors in the human brain.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6492486</pmid>
      <title>Study on the striatal dopamine availability in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1801100</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse: an animal model of olivopontocerebellar atrophy.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1378662</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor interactions: some implications for the treatment of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3091770</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine metabolism in patients with Parkinson's disease measured with positron emission tomography.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19948166</pmid>
      <title>Beta frequency synchronization in basal ganglia output during rest and walk in a hemiparkinsonian rat.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19061540</pmid>
      <title>Central and peripheral dopamine transporter reduction in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9620058</pmid>
      <title>Polymorphisms of dopamine receptor and transporter genes and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19356748</pmid>
      <title>Semantic activation in Parkinson's disease patients on and off levodopa.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10762131</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-mediated gene regulation in models of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19391152</pmid>
      <title>Visualizing vesicular dopamine dynamics in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12145295</pmid>
      <title>Effect of mutant alpha-synuclein on dopamine homeostasis in a new human mesencephalic cell line.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10401786</pmid>
      <title>Levodopa induces a cytoplasmic localization of D1 dopamine receptors in striatal neurons in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3024663</pmid>
      <title>An examination of parkinsonian versus anhedonia contributions to self-stimulation impairments induced by dopamine dysfunction.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8248849</pmid>
      <title>Low density of dopamine D4 receptors in Parkinson's, schizophrenia, and control brain striata.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19070633</pmid>
      <title>Systemic lipopolysaccharide plus MPTP as a model of dopamine loss and gait instability in C57Bl/6J mice.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="77">
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10570493</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine release from nigral transplants visualized in vivo in a Parkinson's patient.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11498597</pmid>
      <title>Expectation and dopamine release: mechanism of the placebo effect in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12706913</pmid>
      <title>Parkinsonian speech disfluencies: effects of L-dopa-related fluctuations.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17017511</pmid>
      <title>Striatal plasticity in parkinsonism: dystrophic changes in medium spiny neurons and progression in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1729408</pmid>
      <title>Aging produces a specific pattern of striatal dopamine loss: implications for the etiology of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20679593</pmid>
      <title>Effects of expectation on placebo-induced dopamine release in Parkinson disease.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12846971</pmid>
      <title>PET studies on the function of dopamine in health and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19896832</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and synaptic plasticity in dorsal striatal circuits controlling action selection.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20645881</pmid>
      <title>New small molecules for the treatment of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2243012</pmid>
      <title>Decreased dopamine in the retinas of patients with Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12915070</pmid>
      <title>Organization of midbrain dopamine systems and the pathophysiology of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21256185</pmid>
      <title>Impaired dopamine release and uptake in R6/1 Huntington's disease model mice.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1772579</pmid>
      <title>A study of brain dopamine sulfate levels in relation to free dopamine and homovanillic acid in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18267275</pmid>
      <title>Positron emission tomography in premotor Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15362717</pmid>
      <title>Changes of dopamine turnover in the progression of Parkinson's disease as measured by positron emission tomography: their relation to disease-compensatory mechanisms.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9126143</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine synthesis, uptake, metabolism, and receptors: relevance to gene therapy of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7754301</pmid>
      <title>Behavior-related activity of primate dopamine neurons.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7699411</pmid>
      <title>Clinical application of neuronal grafts in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16140639</pmid>
      <title>Developmental pesticide models of the Parkinson disease phenotype.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15681811</pmid>
      <title>The degeneration of dopamine neurons in Parkinson's disease: insights from embryology and evolution of the mesostriatocortical system.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11261503</pmid>
      <title>Biochemical variations in the synaptic level of dopamine precede motor fluctuations in Parkinson's disease: PET evidence of increased dopamine turnover.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930746</pmid>
      <title>CNS compensation to dopamine neuron loss in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15710494</pmid>
      <title>Impaired acquisition of skilled behavior in rotarod task by moderate depletion of striatal dopamine in a pre-symptomatic stage model of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9497616</pmid>
      <title>[How can PET scan be used in Parkinson disease?].
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19070633</pmid>
      <title>Systemic lipopolysaccharide plus MPTP as a model of dopamine loss and gait instability in C57Bl/6J mice.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8714754</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors--the present state of research and perspectives.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10762131</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-mediated gene regulation in models of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9349549</pmid>
      <title>In vivo electrochemical measurement of the long-lasting release of dopamine and serotonin induced by intrastriatal kainic acid.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12557287</pmid>
      <title>Plasticity of the nigropallidal pathway in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8041491</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine induces apoptosis-like cell death in cultured chick sympathetic neurons--a possible novel pathogenetic mechanism in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>5355341</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine (3-hydroxytyramine) metabolism in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17017561</pmid>
      <title>Placebo effect and dopamine release.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19356748</pmid>
      <title>Semantic activation in Parkinson's disease patients on and off levodopa.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>14870689</pmid>
      <title>[A comparative study of efficacy of dopamine receptors agonists and catechol-O-methyltransferase in the treatment of late stages of Parkinson's disease].
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11388662</pmid>
      <title>Cell therapy and transplantation in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="80">
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17017511</pmid>
      <title>Striatal plasticity in parkinsonism: dystrophic changes in medium spiny neurons and progression in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20977677</pmid>
      <title>Proteomic analysis of dopamine and alpha-synuclein interplay in a cellular model of Parkinson's disease pathogenesis.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7062116</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1801100</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse: an animal model of olivopontocerebellar atrophy.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21182589</pmid>
      <title>P25alpha / TPPP expression increases plasma membrane presentation of the dopamine transporter and enhances cellular sensitivity to dopamine toxicity.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9620058</pmid>
      <title>Polymorphisms of dopamine receptor and transporter genes and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12192006</pmid>
      <title>Metalloenzyme-like activity of Alzheimer's disease beta-amyloid. Cu-dependent catalytic conversion of dopamine, cholesterol, and biological reducing agents to neurotoxic H(2)O(2).
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8714754</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors--the present state of research and perspectives.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1729408</pmid>
      <title>Aging produces a specific pattern of striatal dopamine loss: implications for the etiology of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10762131</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-mediated gene regulation in models of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9747462</pmid>
      <title>In vivo expression of therapeutic human genes for dopamine production in the caudates of MPTP-treated monkeys using an AAV vector.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7509865</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in a genetic mouse model of Lesch-Nyhan disease.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12145295</pmid>
      <title>Effect of mutant alpha-synuclein on dopamine homeostasis in a new human mesencephalic cell line.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19070633</pmid>
      <title>Systemic lipopolysaccharide plus MPTP as a model of dopamine loss and gait instability in C57Bl/6J mice.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21474106</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine controls neurogenesis in the adult salamander midbrain in homeostasis and during regeneration of dopamine neurons.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10829080</pmid>
      <title>Severe deficiencies in dopamine signaling in presymptomatic Huntington's disease mice.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8104554</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor pharmacology.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16243049</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine dependency of cognitive switching and response repetition effects in Parkinson's patients.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9886073</pmid>
      <title>Influence of age and strain on striatal dopamine loss in a genetic mouse model of Lesch-Nyhan disease.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18781680</pmid>
      <title>Striatal and extrastriatal dopamine in the basal ganglia: an overview of its anatomical organization in normal and Parkinsonian brains.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17290452</pmid>
      <title>Higher nigrostriatal dopamine neuron loss in early than late onset Parkinson's disease?--a [99mTc]-TRODAT-1 SPECT study.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12915048</pmid>
      <title>Novel anti-inflammatory therapy for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15681811</pmid>
      <title>The degeneration of dopamine neurons in Parkinson's disease: insights from embryology and evolution of the mesostriatocortical system.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19061540</pmid>
      <title>Central and peripheral dopamine transporter reduction in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10430830</pmid>
      <title>The substantia nigra of the human brain. II. Patterns of loss of dopamine-containing neurons in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18039462</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine differentially induces aggregation of A53T mutant and wild type alpha-synuclein: insights into the protein chemistry of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10101608</pmid>
      <title>[Behavioral, cellular and molecular consequences of the dopamine transporter gene inactivation].
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15130772</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine toxicity involves mitochondrial complex I inhibition: implications to dopamine-related neuropsychiatric disorders.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17065224</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine enhances motor and neuropathological consequences of polyglutamine expanded huntingtin.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20471298</pmid>
      <title>Trials of neuroprotective therapies for Parkinson's disease: problems and limitations.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1772579</pmid>
      <title>A study of brain dopamine sulfate levels in relation to free dopamine and homovanillic acid in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18348679</pmid>
      <title>Potential therapeutic targets for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17707679</pmid>
      <title>The rationale for continuous dopaminergic stimulation in advanced Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16798054</pmid>
      <title>Estimating the value of novel interventions for Parkinson's disease: an early decision-making model with application to dopamine cell replacement.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19391152</pmid>
      <title>Visualizing vesicular dopamine dynamics in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15297154</pmid>
      <title>Genetic contributions to Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="89">
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20977677</pmid>
      <title>Proteomic analysis of dopamine and alpha-synuclein interplay in a cellular model of Parkinson's disease pathogenesis.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16243049</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine dependency of cognitive switching and response repetition effects in Parkinson's patients.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6147948</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-beta-hydroxylase and acetylcholinesterase activities of cerebrospinal fluid in Alzheimer's disease.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15596613</pmid>
      <title>Lack of regional selectivity during the progression of Parkinson disease: implications for pathogenesis.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15130772</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine toxicity involves mitochondrial complex I inhibition: implications to dopamine-related neuropsychiatric disorders.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10101608</pmid>
      <title>[Behavioral, cellular and molecular consequences of the dopamine transporter gene inactivation].
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11577238</pmid>
      <title>Dendrodendritic inhibition through reversal of dopamine transport.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20013480</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic modulation of the planning phase of skill acquisition in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12689773</pmid>
      <title>Presymptomatic compensation in Parkinson's disease is not dopamine-mediated.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8714754</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors--the present state of research and perspectives.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18781680</pmid>
      <title>Striatal and extrastriatal dopamine in the basal ganglia: an overview of its anatomical organization in normal and Parkinsonian brains.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16944357</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic action beyond its effects on motor function: imaging studies.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9886073</pmid>
      <title>Influence of age and strain on striatal dopamine loss in a genetic mouse model of Lesch-Nyhan disease.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10220107</pmid>
      <title>Cytotoxic and genotoxic potential of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11436352</pmid>
      <title>Gene therapy for Parkinson's disease: determining the genes necessary for optimal dopamine replacement in rat models.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9771125</pmid>
      <title>[Functional role and pharmacological regulation of the dopaminergic system of the brain].
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17575584</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine levels after repetitive transcranial magnetic stimulation of motor cortex in patients with Parkinson's disease: preliminary results.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18325544</pmid>
      <title>Spreading activation of lexical-semantic networks in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9749797</pmid>
      <title>Reduction of noradrenaline impairs attention and dopamine depletion slows responses in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11403185</pmid>
      <title>Striatal dopamine transporter binding in early to moderately advanced Parkinson's disease: monitoring of disease progression over 2 years.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19793590</pmid>
      <title>Therapy adherence issues in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19070633</pmid>
      <title>Systemic lipopolysaccharide plus MPTP as a model of dopamine loss and gait instability in C57Bl/6J mice.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21474106</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine controls neurogenesis in the adult salamander midbrain in homeostasis and during regeneration of dopamine neurons.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15845424</pmid>
      <title>The dopamine transporter: role in neurotoxicity and human disease.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15350965</pmid>
      <title>Synergistic effects of dopamine and Zn2+ on the induction of PC12 cell death and dopamine depletion in the striatum: possible implication in the pathogenesis of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21212609</pmid>
      <title>[Regulation of dopaminergic neuronal death by endogenous dopamine and proteasome activity].
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>2387158</pmid>
      <title>Distractibility in early Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930746</pmid>
      <title>CNS compensation to dopamine neuron loss in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1823144</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for plasticity of the dopaminergic system in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12207999</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and the representation of the upper visual field: evidence from vertical bisection errors in unilateral Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8104554</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor pharmacology.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17652581</pmid>
      <title>Dopaminergic signaling and striatal neurodegeneration in Huntington's disease.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>7509865</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in a genetic mouse model of Lesch-Nyhan disease.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1801100</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine deficiency in the weaver mutant mouse: an animal model of olivopontocerebellar atrophy.
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9620058</pmid>
      <title>Polymorphisms of dopamine receptor and transporter genes and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>50</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18039462</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine differentially induces aggregation of A53T mutant and wild type alpha-synuclein: insights into the protein chemistry of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
  <topic id="90">
    <article>
      <pmid>11102464</pmid>
      <title>Estrogen is essential for maintaining nigrostriatal dopamine neurons in primates: implications for Parkinson's disease and memory.
</title>
      <rank>1</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8464534</pmid>
      <title>Brain dopamine receptors: 20 years of progress.
</title>
      <rank>2</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>16719623</pmid>
      <title>The influence of dopamine on semantic activation in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a multipriming task.
</title>
      <rank>3</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1387567</pmid>
      <title>Multiple dopamine receptors and their implications in medicine.
</title>
      <rank>4</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12428719</pmid>
      <title>Functional imaging of the dopamine system: in vivo evaluation of dopamine deficiency and restoration.
</title>
      <rank>5</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11068137</pmid>
      <title>Role of oxidative changes in the degeneration of dopamine terminals after injection of neurotoxic levels of dopamine.
</title>
      <rank>6</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10353107</pmid>
      <title>External radioactive reference markers in SPECT imaging of the dopamine system.
</title>
      <rank>7</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20977677</pmid>
      <title>Proteomic analysis of dopamine and alpha-synuclein interplay in a cellular model of Parkinson's disease pathogenesis.
</title>
      <rank>8</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11619865</pmid>
      <title>From DOPA to Parkinson's disease: the early history of dopamine research.
</title>
      <rank>9</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>18471904</pmid>
      <title>Altered vesicular dopamine storage in Parkinson's disease: a premature demise.
</title>
      <rank>10</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3550516</pmid>
      <title>Brain grafting as a treatment for Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>11</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8848171</pmid>
      <title>Involvement of ventrolateral striatal dopamine in movement initiation and execution: a microdialysis and behavioral investigation.
</title>
      <rank>12</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11823721</pmid>
      <title>Increase in dopamine turnover occurs early in Parkinson's disease: evidence from a new modeling approach to PET 18 F-fluorodopa data.
</title>
      <rank>13</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11711873</pmid>
      <title>A novel mechanism of dopamine neurotoxicity involving the peripheral extracellular and the plasma membrane dopamine transporter.
</title>
      <rank>14</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>930745</pmid>
      <title>The Parkinsonian syndrome and its dopamine correlates.
</title>
      <rank>15</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9380041</pmid>
      <title>The dopamine transporter: a crucial component regulating dopamine transmission.
</title>
      <rank>16</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9620058</pmid>
      <title>Polymorphisms of dopamine receptor and transporter genes and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>17</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9747462</pmid>
      <title>In vivo expression of therapeutic human genes for dopamine production in the caudates of MPTP-treated monkeys using an AAV vector.
</title>
      <rank>18</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>20188048</pmid>
      <title>[Recent discoveries on the function and plasticity of central dopamine pathways].
</title>
      <rank>19</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1823144</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for plasticity of the dopaminergic system in parkinsonism.
</title>
      <rank>20</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8714754</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptors--the present state of research and perspectives.
</title>
      <rank>21</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19853009</pmid>
      <title>Grafted dopamine neurons: Morphology, neurochemistry, and electrophysiology.
</title>
      <rank>22</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1772579</pmid>
      <title>A study of brain dopamine sulfate levels in relation to free dopamine and homovanillic acid in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>23</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3352672</pmid>
      <title>Uneven pattern of dopamine loss in the striatum of patients with idiopathic Parkinson's disease. Pathophysiologic and clinical implications.
</title>
      <rank>24</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19356748</pmid>
      <title>Semantic activation in Parkinson's disease patients on and off levodopa.
</title>
      <rank>25</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>1729408</pmid>
      <title>Aging produces a specific pattern of striatal dopamine loss: implications for the etiology of idiopathic Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>26</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>15130772</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine toxicity involves mitochondrial complex I inhibition: implications to dopamine-related neuropsychiatric disorders.
</title>
      <rank>27</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6147948</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-beta-hydroxylase and acetylcholinesterase activities of cerebrospinal fluid in Alzheimer's disease.
</title>
      <rank>28</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8104554</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine receptor pharmacology.
</title>
      <rank>29</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12459860</pmid>
      <title>Induction of immune complexes and autoantibodies to serotonin and dopamine in patients with Alzheimer's disease.
</title>
      <rank>30</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19765180</pmid>
      <title>Neuronal cell replacement in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>31</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12846971</pmid>
      <title>PET studies on the function of dopamine in health and Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>32</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17017511</pmid>
      <title>Striatal plasticity in parkinsonism: dystrophic changes in medium spiny neurons and progression in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>33</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6128037</pmid>
      <title>Neuroleptic effects in Tourette syndrome predict dopamine excess and acetylcholine deficiency.
</title>
      <rank>34</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17575584</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine levels after repetitive transcranial magnetic stimulation of motor cortex in patients with Parkinson's disease: preliminary results.
</title>
      <rank>35</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17371292</pmid>
      <title>Movement without dopamine: striatal dopamine is required to maintain but not to perform learned actions.
</title>
      <rank>36</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>19896832</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine and synaptic plasticity in dorsal striatal circuits controlling action selection.
</title>
      <rank>37</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>3165432</pmid>
      <title>Continuous intracerebroventricular infusion of dopamine and dopamine agonists through a totally implanted drug delivery system in animal models of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>38</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>8010587</pmid>
      <title>Cellular and molecular mechanisms of impaired dopaminergic function during aging.
</title>
      <rank>39</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11514985</pmid>
      <title>Evidence for target-specific outgrowth from subpopulations of grafted human dopamine neurons.
</title>
      <rank>40</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17046697</pmid>
      <title>Rapid alterations in corticostriatal ensemble coordination during acute dopamine-dependent motor dysfunction.
</title>
      <rank>41</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>6223322</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine autoreceptor stimulation: clinical significance.
</title>
      <rank>42</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>14678778</pmid>
      <title>ALDH1 mRNA: presence in human dopamine neurons and decreases in substantia nigra in Parkinson's disease and in the ventral tegmental area in schizophrenia.
</title>
      <rank>43</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>21259269</pmid>
      <title>Cell transplantation and gene therapy in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>44</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>12706913</pmid>
      <title>Parkinsonian speech disfluencies: effects of L-dopa-related fluctuations.
</title>
      <rank>45</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>11515746</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine transporter immunoreactivity in peripheral blood lymphocytes in Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>46</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>10762131</pmid>
      <title>Dopamine-mediated gene regulation in models of Parkinson's disease.
</title>
      <rank>47</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17617387</pmid>
      <title>Alterations in striatal dopamine catabolism precede loss of substantia nigra neurons in a mouse model of juvenile neuronal ceroid lipofuscinosis.
</title>
      <rank>48</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17380778</pmid>
      <title>[Placebo effect in Parkinson's disease].
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>17315755</pmid>
      <title>[Placebo effect in Parkinson's disease].
</title>
      <rank>49</rank>
    </article>
    <article>
      <pmid>9367266</pmid>
      <title>Estrogen decreases corpus striatal neurotoxicity in response to 6-hydroxydopamine.
</title>
      <rank>51</rank>
    </article>
  </topic>
</articles>
